{
    "subject": "resource/Simcere_Pharmaceutical",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Simcere Pharmaceutical",
    "human_readable": "Simcere Pharmaceutical is named Simcere Pharmaceutical.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9203402996063232,
            "question": "Who are the founders of Simcere Pharmaceutical?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8943260312080383,
            "question": "What type of company is Simcere Pharmaceutical?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8902695775032043,
            "question": "Is Simcere Pharmaceutical a real company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.797273576259613,
            "question": "What products or services does Simcere Pharmaceutical offer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7775106430053711,
            "question": "Is there any public information available about Simcere Pharmaceutical?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7678337097167969,
            "question": "What is the history of Simcere Pharmaceutical?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7518177032470703,
            "question": "Does Simcere Pharmaceutical operate in the healthcare industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7298488020896912,
            "question": "Where is Simcere Pharmaceutical headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7170577049255371,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Simcere Pharmaceutical?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39586207270622253,
            "question": "What is the name of the pharmaceutical company?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Simcere Pharmaceutical is named Simcere Pharmaceutical.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8099_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Simcere Pharmaceutical?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8099_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Simcere Pharmaceutical headquartered?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8099_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Simcere Pharmaceutical operate in the healthcare industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8099_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8099_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8099_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8099_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8099_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8099_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8099_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8099_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8099_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8099_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8099_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{ \"output\": \"yes\" }\n\nThe documents mention \"Simcere Pharmaceutical Group Limited\", which matches the name given in the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly reference \"Simcere Pharmaceutical Group Limited\" and provide detailed information about the company, including its name. Therefore, the statement \"Simpcer Pharmaceutical is named Simcere Pharmaceutical\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}